Finding aid for the L.A. Rebellion Collection LSC.2429
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Julie Dash papers, 1972-2009
  - Subseries 2.5: Correspondence, film catalogs, and ephemera, 1972-2009
    This subseries contains materials otherwise relating to Dash and her films. This includes correspondence to Dash about her films, support and rejection letters, film catalogs advertising her films, and administrative paperwork relating to her time as a student at UCLA.
    - UCLA MFA paperwork, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Funny Valentines press and promotional material, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence to Dash regarding screenings, 1977-2009 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Letters from Alice Walker to Dash, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence to Dash, 1986-1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Support letters and rejection letters, 1976-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Daughters of the Dust kudos letters, 1980-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with AFI regarding Illusions, 1974-1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence with Guggenheim Memorial Foundation regarding Illusions, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Letters to Dash from Fugitive Cinema Holland, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Film catalogs, 1972-1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Film catalogs, 1982-2009 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Women's film catalog, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - CinémAction book, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Signed copy of Incognito book by Francis Ray, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Artists for Democracy (Haiti), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Unlabeled photographs, 3D glasses, Funny Valentines stills, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Black women in media arts calendars, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Whitney Museum biennial exhibition book, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Julie Dash ephemera, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)